AARON BOOTH

Charlotte, NC 28227

Phone: 704-962-9817| Email: abooth9422@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abooth9422/ Github: https://github.com/ABooth9422

Portfolio: https://abooth9422.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with over a decade experience in Retail Management and a dedication to learning new technologies. Effective at combining creativity and creative problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among staff and peers for strong determination and attention to detail when executing projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Group Technical Skills into categories without bullet points or tables. See sample categories. Languages:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React.js, Node.js, C#, .Net, Database Theory, Bookshelf.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, and Git.

PROJECTS

Tattoo4U| github.com/ABooth9422/Project1 | abooth9422.github.io/Project1

We wanted to make it easy for people to be able to locate tattoo shops based on the "style" that they are interested in. A lot of people that want a tattoo do not know how to properly research who is right to do that tattoo. With our application you will be able to search the local shops in the area that is selected and the results for the style selected will display the tattoo shop which is deemed to specialize in that style.

- The core responsibility I had in the project was the design and making sure that the Results that came back from the AJAX calls were formatted appropriately for the site.
- Languages used: CSS, Javascript, JQuery
- Technologies used: Mapquest API, Yelp API, Google Firebase

Designated Kicker | github.com/ABooth9422/Project 2 | blooming-atoll-38469.herokuapp.com

The goal of this project was for an inventor to take the idea they may have to see if it had been done before. We use our custom search to look for the results based on the users input or not to see if someone has invented a product like theres or a similar idea. After the user sees the results we give them an opportunity to host there project through us.

- In the project I was responsible for handling the front end design as well as the routes for when the server would respond and what content would show from the server.
- Languages used: CSS, Javascript, JQuery
- Technologies used: Animate.CSS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Node, MySQL, Sequelize, Heroku, Google Custom Search API

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support / Hardware Installer Netsafe Solutions

March 2019- Present Charlotte, NC

Daily responsibilities are to ensure that all customers networks are operational if stationed at the help desk. When a customer calls in to report a problem working with the client to make sure the problem is resolved timely During a customer install to make sure all equipment is functional and make hardware suggestions of what they need to upgrade based on there network setup.

Key Accomplishments:

- Increased Sales by 20% with on-site installs.
- Top Customer satisfaction rating from customer tickets

ADDITION EXPERIENCE

Assistant Store Leader Petsmart

April 2017-March 2019 RockHill, SC

Daily responsibilities were to manage store operations of the business and making sure that all aspects of the operation are functional. Responsible for scheduling, payroll, hiring, terminations, and adhering all employees to company policy with asserting disciplinary action if necessary.

Key Accomplishments:

- Managed Store Operations highest volume store in the district.
- Increased Sales 10% overall for 2018.

General Manager PartyCity

May 2013-April 2017 Charlotte, NC

Daily responsibilities were to manage assistant managers and make sure that the business was meeting sales goals. Effectively managed team to hit deadlines with projects with resetting the store each season as the business was based on holidays. Also responsible for scheduling, payroll, ordering, custom order requests, hiring, terminations, and enforcing company policy.

Key Accomplishments:

- Lead all four years successful Halloween Seasons with an increase of 10% each year.
- Highest Sales day in the district 2016 low volume store achieved \$65k in one sales day.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: UNCC, Charlotte, NC

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

High School Diploma: Vance High School, Charlotte, NC